<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>All Posts - Jiajian Fu&#39;s site</title>
        <link>https://jiajianfu.github.io/posts/</link>
        <description>All Posts | Jiajian Fu&#39;s site</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>Jiajian.Fu@qq.com (Jiajian Fu)</managingEditor>
            <webMaster>Jiajian.Fu@qq.com (Jiajian Fu)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 16:04:05 &#43;0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jiajianfu.github.io/posts/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Robot Design｜MX_2 Engineer</title>
    <link>https://jiajianfu.github.io/posts/mx_2_engineer/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 16:04:05 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Jiajian Fu</author>
    <guid>https://jiajianfu.github.io/posts/mx_2_engineer/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Introduction to Robot Design Background The core task of the engineer robot is to obtain gold ore from the large resource island in the center of the field and silver ore from the small resource island, and complete the exchange at the exchange station to obtain economic support for the whole team. This season, the method of exchanging ore for projects has changed a lot. The exchange station has been]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>MechaX：About Us</title>
    <link>https://jiajianfu.github.io/posts/second_post/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 15:38:28 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Jiajian Fu</author>
    <guid>https://jiajianfu.github.io/posts/second_post/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Who Are We？ MechaX is a robotics team established on the basis of the X-Innovation Center of Chongqing University. Its members are undergraduates majoring in mechanics, electrical information, and automation. 2022 Our team has just been built 2023 Our team is growing Filmed outside the RMUC 2023 arena &ldquo;MechaX&rdquo; is the newly launched team name of the Robot team in the 2022 season. It is more in line]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>MechaX Robots Overview</title>
    <link>https://jiajianfu.github.io/posts/first_post/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 16:55:03 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Jiajian Fu</author>
    <guid>https://jiajianfu.github.io/posts/first_post/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[The display and introduction of all the Robots of the MechaX in the 2023 season 0. The Competition Rules of RoboMaster University Championship（RMUC）2023 1. MX_1 Hero Hero Launches 42mm projectiles to cause tremendous damage to the opponents 2. MX_2 Engineer Engineer Features flexible structure, competes for minerals to gain]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
